Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
A brutal invasion shattered the peace of the Clover Kingdom's capital.
Fire blazed in five areas of the city, and the Magic Knights mobilized immediately to calm its panicking populace.
They soon found themselves battling hordes of unfamiliar foes.
This time you're gonna have to come after me yourself!
Think you've got me beat now, do you?
No way, boy!
Come forth, help me!
Now, number two! Say hi to Alfred! Go and get him, Alfred! He's all yours!
...
Oh
That's odd
They may be great in number, but they are poor fighters
Who is commanding them?
Why employ such a strategy?
What are they after?
The King?
Why isn't the Wizard King himself here?
These are the gravers of circumstances
And yet he fails to do his sworn duty
Whatever errand he was on
He should have run immediately to my side
At the first hint that the capital was being threatened
His primary task is to safeguard the royal person from any and all harm
As our mightiest mage, the Wizard King is responsible for my well-being above all else
Has he forgotten that?
I assure you, he hasn't
Sire, we of the Wizard King's staff will be here to guard you until he can return
Oh, that Julius!
We share authority and military matters
And he thinks that means he can do whatever he pleases
Arrogant pup
Sometimes he seems to forget that this kingdom has but one ruler
Augustus Kyra Clover is king here
Not Julius Novocrono
What are you still doing here, Chef?
The capital is under attack
We need to get to safety, quickly
You fool!
I would never turn tail and run during the middle of a dish
I am a chef
A little invasion won't stop me from completing this feast
All due respect, sir, but I'm afraid the banquet's over
The magic knights have all gone down to the city to fight
There's no one for us to serve
What?!
They had the nerve to leave without even trying my entree
It is a national emergency
Which means we need to get out
Hey!
Where did this little shortcake come from?
You've mentioned a special entree, Chef
Huh?
I'd be honored if you'd let me try it for you!
A magic knight robe
She must be one of the big shots from the Distinguished Service Ceremony
Look at her
Those eyes ablaze with determination
That drool sparkling with desperation
This one is something special
I hope you're hungry!
Just you wait
I'll make you a dish that will ruin you for all other food
You can't be serious, sir!
We don't have time for this! We'll die!
I'm not afraid of death
Life is life! Cooking is all!
Poor little brat! It looks like you're having some trouble!
That rusty anti-magic sword of yours is failing you!
It's nothing more than a hunk of metal if you can't hit your target!
Please don't get hit!
Quick run!
Get away from there!
Okay...
But he needs help too!
Everything will be alright
Leave it to me
Don't worry
I would never abandon someone like that
Come on! Get down here!
Did you really think that would work?
He's not going to stand still just because you asked him to, you idiot!
Back when we were in the dungeon
Yeah, I'll bring this guy down
And I'll get one or two hits in for you while I'm at it
I may not have any magic power
But what I do have
ARE MY FRIENDS!
When his sword was imbued with my magic, Asta defeated that mage
If I lend him my power again, even an enemy in mid-air should be no problem
Black bull girl
If you're going to step in and assist your squad mate, I will accompany you
I won't allow that coward to harm my rival
Great
A playmate for you!
That should keep you occupied!
Such muddy magic...
Not a good match with mine
Basta!
That wound he got earlier looks bad!
Huh?
Hey brat!
Remember what you said earlier?
That stuff about me coming after you myself!
Don't you get it?
Why would I bother fighting you myself?
I've got plenty of others to do it for me!
I just have to sit back and watch!
That way I achieve maximum results with minimum risk!
The plus son of not being a muscle-bond moron!
I've got plenty of others to do it for me!
I just have to sit back and watch!
That way I achieve maximum results with minimum risk!
The plus son of not being a muscle-bond moron!
I not only have a brain, but I know how to use it!
Something you can't do it for me!
That way I achieve maximum results with minimum risk!
The plus son of not being a muscle-bond moron!
I not only have a brain, but I know how to use it!
Something you can't say!
Hey idiot!
Sorry!
And 3% more people have money!
Who are going to even manage?
Let them not be a bunch of aructive banana arms!
I'll do it for myself!
It's pretty Für than about!
I'll have plenty of others to do it for me!
I'll do it for you!
What should I do?
This guy is more of a monster than a human being.
I can't let him win.
What are you thinking about over there?
How to defeat me?
Stop wasting your time!
Nothing's going to save you now!
Alfred!
Asta!
Damn it.
Now what?
Finish him!
No!
Impossible!
My Alfred!
Reduced the cinders with one strike!
It was him.
What's wrong with me?
Why couldn't I beat him?
I wanted to do it on my own.
I interfered in your fight.
It was necessary.
I'm sorry.
I thought it a pity for a magic knight of your caliber to die here.
Forgive me.
I will say, though, for a commoner with no magic, you handled yourself well against a difficult enemy.
You know, kid, I like you.
Come join our crew.
He was right.
It pains me to admit it, but Yami showed greater foresight than the rest of us.
Asta, you said you planned to become the wizard king.
You said you planned to become the wizard king.
You said you could be the magic knight of your country.
What?
You think that you could be the wizard king?
Whatever anti-magic abilities you have, you're a brainless brat!
You'll never amount to anything!
Asta.
It seems that I am your rival as well.
Interesting turn of events.
The Black Bullboy couldn't handle it,
so it looks like I've got a new opponent.
None other than the Captain of the Crimson Lion Kings.
The Great Quagolion Vermillion!
You've done enough.
You can leave the rest to me now.
He's all right.
My brother's got this.
Did he really mean what he said before?
It seems that I am your rival as well.
A Captain's rival? No way!
Wait!
This is no time to be giving up!
I'll fight with you!
I can keep going!
No you can't!
Like I wasn't already hurt enough!
Exactly.
A warrior must always be aware of his body's condition.
He must assess whether or not he is truly able to fight.
Right now I would say that you most likely are not.
Your brash fearlessness may well be the greatest weapon you have,
but you must learn to remain calm.
That is if you truly do wish to be the Wizard King.
Tell me, what is the purpose of this attack?
Your actions are too inconsistent for this to be a true invasion,
and too organized for it to be some sort of terrorism.
Just who are you?
You really don't know.
Well, I can't say I'm surprised.
Though it's a shame I'm the only one enjoying this reunion.
What's that?
I was a magic knight, inducted six years ago as a top candidate.
One of us.
No, that can't be possible.
More than possible, I assure you.
Though I suppose you took little note of me at the time.
He's a regular citizen, but his power is incredible.
Do we have any hands, Captains?
It's been a long time, but I remember you.
Your name?
The name's Rades.
Rades, that's right.
You were chosen by the Purple Orcas, so why are you fighting against us now?
Because those short-sighted fools kicked me out.
You were expelled?
That doesn't make sense.
You were strong, had so much potential.
They were frightened by what I could do with my wraith magic.
They said it was dangerous.
Forbidden!
I was exiled not just from my squad, but from the entire kingdom.
I'm only an average citizen.
No one cared enough to stand up for me!
No one!
I was beneath them.
It didn't matter that my skills were greater!
Greater than the nobles!
Greater than anyone's!
Magic is supposed to be everything, and yet they cast me aside!
Fools!
There you have it, Captain.
I'm here to use my cursed power to get revenge on the magic knights.
And the kingdom that rejected me.
That is the purpose of this attack.
Well, that's one of the purposes anyway.
All of this just to get your revenge?
Don't toy with me!
You fool!
You doubt me?
Ha!
That's the thing about reasons.
They're usually quite simple.
Leo!
Right here, brother!
Do you need any help?
Nope!
We've got this under control!
Don't worry about us!
Hey!
Alright then!
You take care of that creature while I handle the mage!
Yes, sir!
Wow!
These guys are hardcore!
Real warrior brothers!
You don't actually think that's going to work!
Their magics are too mismatched for a decent fight!
Not that I was going to let you help!
They're on their own!
That's enough talking!
Time to fight!
Flame creation magic!
Leo Rutians!
The Wraith shielded itself!
Meet my number one, Carl!
This fellow was extremely good at defensive magic back when he was alive!
With a dash of my curse powers thrown in, we're practically impervious!
Geez, another one?
How many does he have?
Asta!
Sir!
Remember what I said before, about staying calm.
Pay close attention!
You're so sure you'll come out on top, aren't you?
Defensive magic isn't the only area in which he excels!
Flame creation magic!
Ignis Kalimna!
So, you've got yourself a magic barrier just like Carl, huh?
Fine!
Let's see how well you hold up when we combine an ironclad defense with a rapid fire attack!
Indeed, I appear to be quite helpless!
Ah, is that all you've got?
I have to say, Captain, I'm very disappointed in you!
I'm very disappointed in you!
Huh?
My flame magic, Solenya.
When you attacked, the mana grew thin in some places across the barrier for the briefest moment.
Those were the spots I aimed for.
You think I've never been up against that sort of attack before?
Listen up, you two!
You are magic knights!
In the line of duty, you will constantly face strong foes and tricky magic!
You must calmly judge your abilities and those of your enemy.
Fight bravely, but keep a cool head and maintain control!
It's not easy, but if you can do that, you will not lose!
Understood?
Yes, sir!
That quickly, he zeroed in on the enemy's weakness and managed to reassure his allies?
So, that's what it means to be a magic knight squad, Captain.
Man!
He's awesome!
No!
It can't be!
He beat my number one wraith so easily!
I should've won, not him!
Listen to me, Radies.
Huh?
You have incredible talent, as well as powerful magic.
But wielded without a just spirit, they are no more than savagery!
You're a monster!
They were right to have expelled you!
Huh?
I have a report, sire.
Almost all of the assailants have now been neutralized.
Have they?
Well, it certainly took them long enough.
The magic knights should hone their skills.
Alright then.
And Julius, is he still off gallivanting about somewhere?
He's out on an important mission, sire.
Honestly now, I can't imagine what he could possibly be doing that's more important than protecting me!
It's over.
I'd still like to know what those things were.
Whatever they were, I find it highly unlikely that they were our true enemy today.
This is what happens to people who dare to attack Char!
Serves you right!
The women of the Blue Rose Knights are the only ones who can lay hands on her!
Enough!
You're just asking to be misunderstood.
Only the Blue Rose Knights can touch her tender skin!
Try again, Sol!
What's this?
Are we done already?
Too bad.
I hardly got to play at all.
Something isn't right here.
I guess it's all but over.
Creepy.
So very creepy.
I need to get stronger,
so I can handle something like this more easily.
Amazing!
Such unbelievable strength!
Let's hear it for the Magic Knights, everyone!
Hip hip hooray!
It's a bit early to be celebrating.
The preparations must be nearly complete by now.
Hip hip hooray!
Time for a feast.
Such lively young mana.
Absolutely delicious!
One
Two
Seven
乾いた感情があの日の僕を見つめ 突き動かしてる I give up a place to go
消えそうな光でも闇を照らす力が 繋がって時の流れを変える
色褪せない場所に Break free yourself
終わらない夢を掴むため 進むべき道があるなら Do you wanna drive? Do you wanna drive?
このままどこまででも 僕の命が終わるまで どんな痛みも受け入れよう
We can drive though We can drive though
たとえ明日が見えなくても 声にならない
想いを抱いて 叫び続ける今
クローバクリップス
3 Second Courtly Cooking
Hello everyone! Clover Kingdom's Royal Chef here bringing you easy 3 second recipes even a beginner can make!
Today we're whipping up a 3 second curry!
To keep it simple we'll start with a roux purchased from the market
Then carrots, onions and potatoes
You can add mushrooms or tomatoes if you like
Flavoring your curry with a touch of chocolate or coffee
Can give it more depth
Now simply take your ingredients and
Use magic to dice them up and stew them
The more passion you put into it the better your curry will be
3 seconds and done! Wasn't that easy?
Alright come to mama!
So good!
This has been 3 Second Courtly Cooking with easy recipes that anyone can make!
Just yummy!
See you later!
Impossible!
Will the magic knights please hurry up and do their jobs already?
Black Clover page 24 blackout
As ruler of Clover Kingdom I Augustus Kira Clover the 13th have some important tasks
namely eating and napping